<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days Of Recipes</string>\
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more or less about recipy</string>
    <string name="title_1">Sunrise Smoothie Bliss</string>
    <string name="title_2">Mediterranean Magic Salad</string>
    <string name="title_3">Spicy Chickpea Tacos</string>
    <string name="title_4">Creamy Mushroom Risotto</string>
    <string name="title_5">Thai Basil Chicken Stir-Fry</string>
    <string name="title_6">Berry Burst Pancakes</string>
    <string name="title_7">Quinoa Buddha Bowl</string>
    <string name="title_8">Classic Margherita Pizza</string>
    <string name="title_9">Zesty Lemon Garlic Shrimp</string>
    <string name="title_10">Vegetarian Sushi Rolls</string>
    <string name="title_11">Butternut Squash Soup Elegance</string>
    <string name="title_12">Caramelized Onion and Goat Cheese Tart</string>
    <string name="title_13">Teriyaki Salmon Feast</string>
    <string name="title_14">Stuffed Bell Peppers Extravaganza</string>
    <string name="title_15">Chocolate Lava Cake Surprise</string>
    <string name="title_16">Pesto Pasta Perfection</string>
    <string name="title_17">Hawaiian Luau Chicken Skewers</string>
    <string name="title_18">Caprese Stuffed Avocado</string>
    <string name="title_19">Black Bean and Corn Quesadillas</string>
    <string name="title_20">Blueberry Lemon Cheesecake Bars</string>
    <string name="title_21">Spinach and Feta Stuffed Chicken Breast</string>
    <string name="title_22">Shrimp and Asparagus Stir-Fry</string>
    <string name="title_23">Tomato Basil Bruschetta</string>
    <string name="title_24">Lemon Herb Grilled Swordfish</string>
    <string name="title_25">Sweet Potato and Chickpea Curry</string>
    <string name="title_26">Raspberry Almond Oat Bars</string>
    <string name="title_27">Caprese Pesto Pasta Salad</string>
    <string name="title_28">Chicken Avocado Mango Salad</string>
    <string name="title_29">Cinnamon Sugar Apple Pie Cups</string>
    <string name="title_30">Celebration Chocolate Mousse</string>
    <string name="description_1">Kickstart your culinary journey with a vibrant sunrise smoothie that combines fresh fruits for a burst of energy.</string>
    <string name="description_2">Transport your taste buds to the Mediterranean with a refreshing and nutritious salad featuring a medley of flavors.</string>
    <string name="description_3">Spice things up with these flavorful and protein-packed chickpea tacos that are perfect for a delightful dinner.</string>
    <string name="description_4">Indulge in the rich and creamy goodness of a classic mushroom risotto that promises to be a comforting delight.</string>
    <string name="description_5">Experience the exotic flavors of Thailand with a quick and easy basil chicken stir-fry that\'s bursting with aromatic spices.</string>
    <string name="description_6">Treat yourself to a delightful breakfast with these fluffy pancakes topped with a burst of mixed berries.</string>
    <string name="description_7">Nourish your body with a colorful and wholesome quinoa Buddha bowl packed with nutrient-rich ingredients.</string>
    <string name="description_8">Channel your inner pizzaiolo and create a classic Margherita pizza with a perfect balance of tomato, mozzarella, and basil.</string>
    <string name="description_9">Savor the zing of zesty lemon and garlic in a succulent shrimp dish that\'s quick and easy to prepare.</string>
    <string name="description_10">Dive into the art of sushi-making with these delicious vegetarian rolls, filled with crisp veggies and sushi rice.</string>
    <string name="description_11">Embrace the warmth of a velvety butternut squash soup, perfectly seasoned for a cozy evening meal.</string>
    <string name="description_12">Delight in the harmony of sweet caramelized onions and tangy goat cheese in a savory tart that\'s as elegant as it is delicious.</string>
    <string name="description_13">Elevate your dinner with a teriyaki-glazed salmon dish, marrying the sweetness of teriyaki with the succulence of perfectly cooked salmon.</string>
    <string name="description_14">Enjoy a colorful and flavorful feast with stuffed bell peppers, filled with a medley of grains, veggies, and savory goodness.</string>
    <string name="description_15">Indulge your sweet tooth with a decadent chocolate lava cake that oozes rich, molten chocolate from the center.</string>
    <string name="description_16">Toss up a plate of pasta coated in vibrant pesto sauce, adorned with pine nuts and Parmesan for a burst of Italian flavor.</string>
    <string name="description_17">Transport your taste buds to a tropical paradise with these Hawaiian-inspired chicken skewers, grilled to perfection.</string>
    <string name="description_18">Combine the freshness of a classic Caprese salad with the creamy richness of avocado for a delightful and healthy snack.</string>
    <string name="description_19">Create a fiesta of flavors with black bean and corn quesadillas, loaded with gooey cheese and zesty Mexican spices.</string>
    <string name="description_20">Cap off your day with a sweet treat—indulge in the luscious combination of blueberry and lemon in cheesecake bar form.</string>
    <string name="description_21">Elevate your dinner with a sophisticated dish—juicy chicken breasts stuffed with the classic combination of spinach and feta.</string>
    <string name="description_22">Delight your palate with a quick and healthy stir-fry featuring succulent shrimp and crisp asparagus, all infused with savory flavors.</string>
    <string name="description_23">Transport yourself to an Italian trattoria with the freshness of tomato and basil bruschetta, perfect as an appetizer or light meal.</string>
    <string name="description_24">Dive into the world of seafood with grilled swordfish infused with zesty lemon and aromatic herbs for a delightful dining experience.</string>
    <string name="description_25">Warm up your evening with a hearty sweet potato and chickpea curry, brimming with exotic spices and creamy coconut milk.</string>
    <string name="description_26">Satisfy your sweet cravings guilt-free with these wholesome raspberry almond oat bars that make for a perfect snack or dessert.</string>
    <string name="description_27">Combine the freshness of a Caprese salad with the heartiness of pasta in a delightful pasta salad drizzled with pesto.</string>
    <string name="description_28">Refresh your palate with a vibrant and nutritious salad featuring the delightful trio of chicken, avocado, and mango.</string>
    <string name="description_29">Embrace the flavors of fall with mini apple pie cups, sprinkled with cinnamon sugar for a deliciously comforting treat.</string>
    <string name="description_30">Conclude your 30-day culinary adventure with a celebration-worthy chocolate mousse, the perfect finale to a month of delicious recipes.</string>


</resources>